A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Overseas Development, International Training and Research, Office Files of John Howard FA608
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1951-1969, bulk 1951-1966; 1951-1966; I
  - USSR -- ITR Faculty Exchanges Between American and Soviet Universities (Sep 1959 Ex. Comm. meeting), 1953-1961 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- General Correspondence Re: USSR and East European Area, 1951-1954 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- General Correspondence Re: USSR and East European Area, 1955 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- General Correspondence Re: USSR and East European Area and Report Re: ITR in Soviet Areas, 1956 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- General Correspondence Re: USSR and East European Area Incl. Materials on Libraries, Archives, 1957 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- Institute for the Study of the USSR -- Jaan Pennar File (L 63-493), 1963 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- International Training and Research -- Soviet and East European Area -- General, 1958 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- International Training and Research -- Soviet and East European Area -- General, 1959 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- International Training and Research -- Soviet and East European Area -- General, 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- ITR File -- "Costs of the Instruments of the Soviet and East European Area", 1962-1964 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- Soviet and East European Fellowship Conference -- Report Re: Training Fellowship, 1953 October 9-10 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- Soviet Studies in the United States, 1955-1964 (Box 21)
  - USSR -- Soviet Travel Reports Incl. Nevitt Sanford's Report on Trip to Russia, 1959 (Box 21)
  - United Nations -- American Association for the United Nations (A-248), 1952-1954 (Box 21)
  - United Nations -- Carnegie Endowment Study (A-794), 1952-1954 (Box 21)
  - United Nations -- Conferences Re: UN, 1951-1952 (Box 22)
  - United Nations -- General Correspondence Re: UN, 1952-1963 (Box 22)
  - United Nations -- Food and Agriculture Organization -- Land Reform (B-72), 1952-1955 (Box 22)
  - United Nations -- High Commissioner for Refugees (A-877), 1952-1954 (Box 22)
  - United Nations -- Library (A-945), 1952-1959 (Box 22)
  - United Nations -- National Citizens' Committee for UN Day (NY-164), 1951-1952 (Box 22)
  - United Nations -- Studies and Programs Re: International Organization in General, 1952 (Box 22)
  - United Nations -- Study of International Non-Governmental Organizations and Their Cooperation with the UN -- CCNGO (B-93), 1951-1952 (Box 22)
  - United Nations -- U.S. National Commissison for UNESCO -- 6th National Conference (Nov 6-9, 1957), 1957-1964 (Box 22)
  - United Nations -- U.S. Policy with Respect to United Nations May 12-13, 1961 Conference Sponsored by Brookings and SAIS at Department of State (Box 22)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare -- National Defense Education Act, 1958 (folder 1), 1958-1959 (Box 22)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare -- National Defense Education Act (folder 2), 1958-1959 (Box 22)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare -- National Defense Education Act, 1959-1960 (Box 22)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare -- National Defense Education Act Re: Language Studies, 1961 (Box 22)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare -- National Defense Education Act, 1962 (Box 22)
  - United States Department of State -- Foreign Service, 1962 (Box 22)
  - United States Department of State -- Peace Corps, 1961-1963 (Box 22)
  - United States Department of State -- Coombs-Harari -- ITR Recommendations on Education and Cultural Programs of State, 1961-1962 (Box 22)
  - United States Department of State -- General, 1957-1964 (Box 22)
  - United States Department of State -- Retired Foreign Service Officers and Other Government Employees as Prospective Teachers, 1962-1964 (Box 22)
  - University Education -- The Fund for the Advancement of Education -- Board of Directors Meeting Materials, 1961 January 23 (Box 22)
  - V -- General Correspondence, 1952-1966 (Box 22)
  - W -- General Correspondence, Reports, 1952-1966 (Box 22)
  - Washington, University of -- Miscellaneous, 1957-1963 (Box 22)
  - Wesleyan University, 1958-1961 (Box 22)
  - West European Studies -- American University, 1963-1964 (Box 23)
  - West European Studies -- California, University of, 1963 (Box 23)
  - West European Studies -- Conference (May 24-25, 1963) (Box 23)
  - West European Studies -- Conference (Nov 1, 1963) (Box 23)
  - West European Studies -- Swayzee File -- Conference Notes, Trip Itineraries, Correspondence, Reports, 1963-1965 (Box 23)
  - West European Studies -- General File, Cleon O. Swayzee Working Papers, etc., 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - White House Conference on Education, 1965 July 20-21 (Box 23)
  - Windsor, University of, 1965 (Box 23)
  - Wisconsin, University of -- General, 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - World Brotherhood -- Compton-Clinchy, 1953-1958 (Box 23)
  - World Law Fund -- Proposal for General Support (L 66-88), 1966 (Box 23)
  - World Peace Through Law (folder 1), 1964-1966 (Box 23)
  - World Peace Through Law (folder 2), 1964-1966 (Box 23)
  - World University Service, 1961-1962 (Box 23)
  - World University Service, 1962-1965 (Box 23)
  - X-Y -- General Correspondence, 1953-1964 (Box 23)
  - Yale University -- Center for Comparative Study of National Economic Growth and Structure (Lloyd Reynolds Proposal), 1959 (Box 23)
  - Yale University (Sidney Mintz, Chairman, Council of Latin American Studies), 1963-1964 (Box 23)
  - Yale University -- General (folder 1), 1954-1962 (Box 23)
  - Yale University -- General (folder 2), 1954-1962 (Box 23)
  - Yugoslavia, 1961 (Box 23)
  - Z -- General Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 23)